// (Multiple answers - 0)

// Cousin

/* eslint-disable no-unused-vars */
const publish_answers = [true, true, true, true, true, true, true, true];

const blankRound = [
  {
    title: '',
    date: '',
    deadline: '',
    show_answers: false,
    form: true,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[7],
    questions: [
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
      { question: '', answer: '' },
    ],
  },
];

const rounds2 = [
  {
    title: 'Lists - One answer out of many',
    date: '2020/04/04',
    deadline: '2020/04/05 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[7],
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'Winners of at least 3 academy awards for acting (Lead role or supporting role)',
        answer: `
        Katharine Hepburn\n
        Meryle Streep (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Daniel Day-Lewis (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Jack Nicholson\n
        Walter Brennan`,
      },
      {
        question:
          'Tottenham players who scored more than 125 goals for the club',
        answer: `
        Jimmy Greaves\n
      Bobby Smith\n
      Harry Kane\n
      Martin Chivers\n
      Cliff Jones\n
      Jermain Defoe (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      George Hunt\n
      Len Duquemin\n
      Alan Gilzean`,
      },
      {
        question: 'Artists or Groups with more than 10 UK number 1 singles',
        answer: `
        Elvis Presley\n
        The Beatles (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Cliff Richard\n
        Westlife\n
        Madonna\n
        The Shadows\n
        Take That`,
      },
      {
        question: 'Countries outside the UK Richard has visited',
        answer: `
      Ireland\n
      France\n
      Spain\n
      Portugal\n
      Italy\n
      Poland\n
      Belgium\n
      Netherlands\n
      Germany (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Greece\n
      Hungary\n
      Romania\n
      Bulgaria\n
      Austria\n
      Korea\n
      Thailand\n
      Philippines\n
      Japan (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Vietnam\n
      Canada\n
      Czech Republic`,
      },
      {
        question: 'Top 10 produced food crops worldwide',
        answer: `
      Sugarcane\n
      Maize\n
      Rice\n
      Wheat\n
      Potatoes\n
      Soybeans\n
      Cassava (yuca) (Bonus point)\n
      Tomatoes\n
      Bananas (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Sweet Potato`,
      },
      {
        question: 'Non-insect animals with more than 4 legs',
        answer: `
      Octupus\n
      Crab\n
      Starfish\n
      King crab\n
      Spider (Bonus point)\n
      Lobster (Multiple answers - 0)
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Top components that make up air on earth',
        answer: `
      Nitrogen (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Oxygen\n
      Argon (Multiple answers - 0)\n 
      Carbon Dioxide (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Neon\n
      Helium\n
      Methane\n
      Krypton\n
      Water (Bonus point) 
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Biggest moons in the solar system',
        answer: `
      Ganymede (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Titan\n
      Callisto\n
      Io\n
      The Moon (Bonus point)\n
      Europa\n
      Triton\n
      Titania\n
      Rhea\n
      Oberon
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'YouTube Videos with more than 5 billion views',
        answer: `
        Descpacito\n
        Baby Shark Dance (Multiple answers - 0)
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Labour Prime Ministers of the 20th Century',
        answer: `
      Tony Blair\n
      James Callaghan (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Harold Wilson\n
      Clement Atlee\n
      Ramsay MacDonald (Multiple answers - 0)
      `,
      },
      {
        question: '21st Century darts world champions',
        answer: `
       Ted Hankey \n
       John Walton\n
       Tony David\n
       Raymond van Barneveld \n
       Andy Fordham\n
       Jelle Klaasen\n
       Martin Adams\n
       Mark Webster \n
       Martin Adams \n
       Christian Kist \n
       Scott Waites \n
       Stephen Bunting \n
       Scott Mitchell\n
       Glen Durrant\n
       Wayne Warren\n
       Phil Taylor\n
       John Part\n
       Adrian Lewis (Multiple answers - 0)\n
       Michael Van Gerwin\n
       Gary Anderson\n
       Rob Cross\n
       Peter Wright
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Ruling Queens of England',
        answer: `
      Elizabeth I\n
      Lady Jane Grey (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Mary I\n
      Mary II\n
      Matilda\n
      Anne
      `,
      },
      {
        question: `UK's favourite home meals`,
        answer: `
      Spag Bol\n
      Pizza\n
      Roast dinner\n
      Fish fingers\n
      Fish and Chips  (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Beans on Toast
      `,
      },
      {
        question: `Top 10 appearing non-Simpson family Simpson's characters`,
        answer: `
          Apu Nahasapeemapetilon\n
          Milhouse Van Houten (Multiple answers - 0)\n
          Chief Clancy Wiggum\n
          Charles Montgomery Burns (Multiple answers - 0)\n
          Ned Flanders\n
          Seymour Skinner\n
          Moe Syzlak\n
          Kent Brockman\n
          Krusty the Clown (Herschel Shmoikel Pinchas Yerucham Krustofsky) (Bonus point for full name)\n
          Lenny Leonard
        `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Countries with a population greater than 200 million people',
        answer: `
        China\n
        India (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        United States\n
        Indonesia\n
        Pakistan\n
        Brazil\n
        Nigeria\n
        `,
      },
      {
        question: `Non-fictional rulers featured in the titles of Shakespeare's histories`,
        answer: `
        Julius Caesar\n
        Cleopatra\n
        Henry V\n
        Henry IV\n
        Henry VI\n
        Richard III\n
        Henry VIII\n
        King John\n
        Edward III (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Richard III
        `,
      },
      {
        question: `Ingredients in Rick Bayless' Chile Con Carne `,
        answer: `
      Dried chilies\n
      Garlic\n
      Onion (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Oregano\n
      Cumin (Multiple answers - 0)\n
      Lard\n
      Salt\n
      Beef
      `,
      },
      {
        question:
          'British individuals who won multiple gold and/or silver medal winners at the 2012 Summer Olympics',
        answer: `
        Chris Hoy (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Jason Kenny\n
        Charlotte Dujardin\n
        Mo Farah (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Andy Murray\n
        Victoria Pendleton
        `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Seven wonders of the ancient world',
        answer: `
        Great Pyramid of Giza, Egypt\n
        Hanging Gardens of Babylon\n
        Statue of Zeus at Olympia\n
        Temple of Artemis at Ephesus\n
        Mausoleum at Halicarnassus (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Colossus of Rhodes\n
        Lighthouse of Alexandria
      `,
      },
      {
        question: 'Films directed by Quentin Tarantino',
        answer: `
        Reservoir Dogs\n
        Jackie Brown\n
        Kill Bill: Volume 1 (Kill Bill accepted)\n
        Kill Bill: Volume 2\n
        Grindhouse: Death Proof (Death Proof accepted\n
        Inglourious Basterds (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Django Unchained\n
        The Hateful Eight (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        Once Upon a Time in Hollywood
      `,
      },
      {
        question: `BONUS: Richard Todd's favourite national cuisines`,
        answer: `
        Thai\n
        Indian\n
        Italian\n
        Chinese (Multiple answers - 0)\n
        British\n
        Japanese\n
        Levant\n
        Mexican
        `,
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '7. Nursery Rhymes',
    date: '2020/04/03',
    deadline: '2020/04/04 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[6],
    questions: [
      { question: 'How many blind mice were there?', answer: 'Three' },
      { question: 'What did nimble jack jump over?', answer: 'A candle stick' },
      {
        question: 'What was the queen eating in her parlour?',
        answer: 'Bread and honey',
      },
      {
        question: 'Why was the old man thrown down the stairs?',
        answer: `Because he wouldn't say his prayers`,
      },
      {
        question: 'What was the colour of the owl’s and the pussy cat’s boat',
        answer: 'Pea green',
      },
      {
        question: 'To where would you ride a cock horse?',
        answer: 'Banbury Cross',
      },
      { question: 'Who lost her sheep?', answer: 'Little Bo Peep' },
      {
        question: 'What would give to your sons if you had no daughters?',
        answer: 'Hot cross buns',
      },
      { question: 'Who came tumbling after?', answer: 'Jill' },
      {
        question:
          'What was Wee Willy Winkie wearing when he ran through the street?',
        answer: 'Nightgown',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who came to see the nut tree?',
        answer: `The king of Spain's daugher`,
      },
      {
        question: 'For how long had the Pease pudding been in the pot?',
        answer: 'Nine days',
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is going to pay up when rich?',
        answer: 'The bells of Shoreditch',
      },
      {
        question: 'From what did Jack pull the plum?',
        answer: 'A Christmas pie',
      },
      { question: 'Who found the pocket?', answer: 'Kitty Fisher' },
      { question: 'Who could eat no lean?', answer: `Jack Spratt's wife` },
      {
        question: 'Who was warming her pretty little toes?',
        answer: 'Litte Polly Flinders',
      },
      { question: 'Which ladybird escaped the conflagration?', answer: 'Ann' },
      {
        question: 'Who said to whom tomorrow will be Monday?',
        answer: 'Tommy Snooks to Bessy Brooks',
      },
      { question: 'Who did puss look at in London?', answer: 'The Queen' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '6. Chocolates',
    date: '2020/04/02',
    deadline: '2020/04/03 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[5],
    questions: [
      { question: 'Regent or Bond? (7,6)', answer: 'Quality Street' },
      { question: 'Not very practical (4,4)', answer: 'Milk Tray' },
      { question: 'Birthdays, Anniversaries (12)', answer: 'Celebrations' },
      { question: 'Witchcraft (5,5)', answer: 'Black Magic' },
      { question: 'William Tell, V.Cs, Spiderman (6)', answer: 'Heroes' },
      { question: 'Peace, Rambling Rector, Judi Dench (5)', answer: 'Roses' },
      { question: 'Big Bus (6,6)', answer: 'Double Decker' },
      { question: 'University Challenge panellists (8)', answer: 'Smarties' },
      { question: 'It’s not Dad’s (4)', answer: `Mars (get it? Mar's)` },
      { question: 'An off-white pub (5,3)', answer: 'Milky Bar' },
      { question: 'Sh! (5)', answer: 'Wispa' },
      { question: 'A feline uniform (3,3)', answer: 'Kit Kat' },
      { question: 'Outlaw (6)', answer: 'Bandit' },
      { question: 'Travelling musicians (9)', answer: 'Minstrels' },
      { question: 'Reward for Capturing (6)', answer: 'Bounty' },
      { question: 'Whisky taunters (9)', answer: 'Malteasers' },
      { question: 'Joy in Istanbul (7,7)', answer: 'Turkish Delight' },
      { question: 'Theme (5)', answer: 'Topic' },
      { question: 'A noisy stretch of water (5)', answer: 'Flake' },
      { question: '10 Cents (4) or (4,3)', answer: 'Daim (Bar)' },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: `5. Who's line is it anyway?`,
    date: '2020/04/01',
    deadline: '2020/04/02 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[4],
    questions: [
      { question: 'A hand bag', answer: 'Lady Bracknell' },
      {
        question: 'Frankly my dear I don’t give a damn!',
        answer: 'Rhett Butler',
      },
      {
        question: 'I believe it is peace for our time',
        answer: 'Neville Chamberlain',
      },
      { question: 'To infinity and beyond', answer: 'Buzz Lightyear' },
      {
        question: 'Never has so much, been owed by so many, to so few.',
        answer: 'Winston Churchill',
      },
      {
        question:
          'I’m playing all ofthe notes but not necessarily in the right order',
        answer: 'Eric Morecombe',
      },
      { question: 'Four Candles', answer: 'Two Ronnies' },
      {
        question: 'To be or not to be: that is the question?',
        answer: 'Hamlet',
      },
      {
        question: 'Stop throwing those bloody spears at me.',
        answer: 'Peachy Carnehan',
      },
      {
        question: 'That’s one small step for man, one giant leap for mankind',
        answer: 'Neil Armstrong',
      },
      { question: 'The lady’s not for turning', answer: 'Margaret Thatcher' },
      {
        question: 'Kiss me harder or was it Kismet Hardy.',
        answer: 'Horatio Nelson',
      },
      { question: 'I am your father', answer: 'Darth Vader' },
      {
        question: 'Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee',
        answer: 'Mohamed Ali',
      },
      { question: 'I have a dream', answer: 'Dr Martin Luther King' },
      { question: 'Good moaning', answer: 'Officer Crabtree' },
      {
        question: 'We’re going to be in the Hudson',
        answer: 'Captain Chesley "Sully" Sullenberger',
      },
      { question: 'You stupid boy!', answer: 'Captain Mainwaring' },
      {
        question: 'Nice to see you, to see you nice',
        answer: 'Bruce Forsythe',
      },
      {
        question: 'Life is what happens when you are busy making other plans',
        answer: 'John Lennon',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '4. Towns and Cities',
    date: '2020/03/31',
    deadline: '2020/04/01 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[3],

    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Tub full of water',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Bath' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Professor of rollers',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Doncaster' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Witches attempt to meet',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Coventry' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'A Person who is leaving',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Exeter' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'People Rock',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Folkstone' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'A complete bacon',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Fulham' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Ship’s men',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Crewe' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Tying Meat',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Nottingham' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Latest Fortified Wine',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Newport' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Religious Skull',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Holyhead' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Detective clues',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Leeds' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Sounds like Piggot’s town',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Leicester' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Where cattle cross the river',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Oxbridge or Cowbridge' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Almost speechless in front of chips',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Dumfries' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Mothers entrance',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Margate' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'USA President',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Licoln or Washington' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Chocolate bar without that is',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'York' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Fake First Lady',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Evesham' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Rifle',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Winchester or Enfield' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Cook al fresco',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[3] ? 'Sheffield' : ''))(),
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '3. Sleuth Creators - Name the author/creator',
    date: '2020/03/30',
    deadline: '2020/03/31 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[2],
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Morse',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Colin Dexter' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Frost',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'R D Wingfield' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Wexford',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Ruth Rendell' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Poirot',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Agatha Christie' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Foyle',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Anthony Horowitz' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Colombo',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[2] ? 'William Link and Richard Levinson' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Inspector Rebus',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Ian Rankin' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Maigret',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'George Simenon' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Harry Hole',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Jo Nesbo' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Sherlock Holmes',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Sir Arthur Conan Doyle' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Brother Cadfel',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Ellis Peters' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Sam Spade',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Dashiell Hammett' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Philip Marlowe',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Raymond Chandler' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Lord Peter Wimsey',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Dorothy L Sayers' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Jack Reacher',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Lee Child' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Perry Mason',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Erle Stanley Gardner' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Hieronymus “Harry” Bosch',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Michael Connely' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Dick Tracy',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Chester Gould' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Dirk Gently',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'Douglas Adams' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Adam Dalgleish',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[2] ? 'P D James' : ''))(),
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '2. Initial Numbers',
    date: '2020/03/29',
    deadline: '2020/03/30 20:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[1],
    questions: [
      {
        question: '1 W on a U',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '1 Wheel on a Unicycle' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '3 BM',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '3 Blind Mice' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '4 S in a Y',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '4 Seasons in a Year' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '6 S of a C',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '6 Sides of a Cube' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '7 W of the W',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '7 Wonders of the World' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '8 is TC',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '8 is two cubed' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '11 P in a FT',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '11 Players in a Football Team' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '12 S of the Z',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '12 Signs of the Zodiac' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '13 in a BD',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '13 in a Bakers Dozen' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '16 O in a P',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '16 Ounces in a Pound ' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '24 B B in a P',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '4 and 20 Blackbirds baked in a Pie' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '29 D in F in a LY',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '29 Days in February in a Leap Year' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '32 DF at which WF',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1]
            ? '32 Degrees Fahrenheit at which Water Freezes'
            : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '57 HV',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '57 Heinz Varieties' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '64 S on a CB',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '64 Squares on a Chess Board' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '76 T in the BP',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '76 Trombones in the Big Parade' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: '99 RB',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '99 Red Balloons' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '101 D',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '101 Dalmatians' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '1760 Y in a M',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[1] ? '1760 Yards in a Mile' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '9,000,000 B in B',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[1] ? '9 Million Bicycles in Beijing' : '')(),
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: '1. Musicals',
    date: '2020/03/28',
    deadline: '2020/03/29 18:00',
    show_answers: true,
    form: false,
    published: true,
    publish_answers: publish_answers[0],
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'The shrew tamed? (4, 2, 4)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Kiss me Kate' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Spectre in singing event? (3, 7, 2, 3, 5)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Phantom of the opera' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: '_____ Lennox or _____ get your gun or _____ Oakley? (5)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Annie' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question:
          'Enough wives for everybody - well at least one each? (5, 6, 3, 5, 8)',
        answer: (() =>
          publish_answers[0] ? 'Seven Brides for Seven Brothers' : '')(),
      },
      {
        question: 'East enders Flying Squad? (7, 4)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Sweeney Todd' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Notoriety? (4)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Fame' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'World champion racing car driver? (8)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Hamilton' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'US State? (8)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Oklahoma' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Royal Siamese governess makes good? (3, 4, 3, 1)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'The King and I' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Did Maria bring the hills to life? (3, 5, 2, 5)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'The Sound of Music' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Greetings child’s toy? (5, 5)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Hello Dolly' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Threepence? (4, 1, 8)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Half a Sixpence' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Not a tale from the orient? (4, 4, 5)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'West Side Story' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'William Writer? (5, 6)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Billy Elliot' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'The French poor ones? (3, 10)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Les Miserables' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Opposite of North Atlantic? (5, 7)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'South Pacific' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Not your dark gentleman? (2, 4, 4)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'My Fair Lady' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Mother Farrow? (5, 3)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Mamma Mia' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Not dogs? (4)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Cats' : ''))(),
      },
      {
        question: 'Night-time features fast train? (9,7)',
        answer: (() => (publish_answers[0] ? 'Starlight Express' : ''))(),
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default rounds2;
